boogiejack.com 2016-04-06

# BoogieJack.com Privacy Policy

Privacy on the Internet is concern for everyone. I have developed a comprehensive privacy policy to assure you that your privacy is respected. 

## The Short Version

At BoogieJack.com you can be assured your privacy is respected. If you write for any reason, you are not tracked or added to a mailing list. I do have an opt-in mailing list. If you subscribe to it your email address will never be sold, traded or given to anyone. I don't like spam and I don't participate in it. 

I do not use cookies to gather personal information about you. My shopping cart does use cookies to remember your order from one page to the next when you use purchase goods or services. The cart will not work without cookies, but these are temporary cookies and are not tracked. 

BoogieJack.com is partially supported by advertising. No personally identifiable information is shared with advertisers unless you give it to them when you respond to an advertisement. Advertisements may or may not contain cookies if you click on an ad. Cookies, if any are used, are not used to collect personally identifiable information. 

## The Long Version

I've created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate my firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses information gathering and dissemination practices. 

  * This site contains links to other sites. BoogieJack.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other web sites. 
  * This site uses a secure order form for customers to purchase products and services. Visitor contact information and credit card numbers are collected when volunteered by the customer. Contact information is used to send orders to the customer and to notify them of upgrades and new products they may have an interested in. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the purchaser for products and services. No information about the purchaser is stored in permanent databases on the server. All orders are made through a 128-bit secure server, and all orders receive approval from Visa/MasterCard before products or services are rendered. 
  * Cookies are used to remember your order from one page to the next when you use the shopping cart to purchase goods or services. The cart will not work without cookies. 
  * Your IP address is recored to help identify you and your shopping cart if you purchase anything, and to prevent criminals from perpetuating credit card fraud against you or this business. 
  * Occasionally, online surveys ask visitors for demographic information (like age, income level, education, etc). Specific information is not shared in any way with 3rd parties. General information (like 65% of those polled make purchases online, are female, etc.) may be shared with potential advertisers to help them decide if my audience is right for their ad campaign. Again, specific information such as names, email addresses, etc, ARE NEVER SHARED. 
  * Occasional contests are offered where visitors are asked for contact information. The customer's contact information is used to contact the contestant when necessary, such as to notify the winner that they've won. 
  * This site does NOT intentionally collect contact information from children, however, children do have access to contest forms, surveys, and email links in which they may submit information without parental consent or parental knowledge. Such information, if received, will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and is never used for other purposes nor shared with any 3rd parties for any reason. 
  * BoogieJack.com is partially supported by advertising. No personally identifiable information is shared with advertisers unless you give it to them when you respond to an advertisement. Advertisements may or may not contain cookies if you click on an ad. Cookies, if any are used, are not used to collect personally identifiable information. 
  * If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

BoogieJack.com  
5607 Riverview Ct.  
Stevens Point, WI 54481  

Or, by email: . 

| 

### Other Site Info Pages

  * FAQ Page
  * Press Room
  * Advertising
  * Refund Policy
  * Copyright Policy
  * Writing Services
  * About BoogieJack.com
  * The Story Behind BoogieJack.com

### Almost a Newsletter

Subscribe today and get a free gift, _The Science of Getting Rich_. Learn more, or subcribe below: 

### Did you know...

The member's site has about 100 standards compliant HTML and CSS tutorials, 31 handy reference charts, reprintable content, web graphics, exclusive fonts, free software, free ebooks and more? All this for less than 9 cents a day!  [Details ]   
Home | Web Design Tutorials | Free Graphics | Newsletter | Products | Specials | SEO | Sound Effects | Press Room   
Sitemap | Member Perks | Member Login | About BoogieJack.com | Contact | Privacy Policy | Copyright Policy | Links

Copyright BoogieJack.com 1997 - 2020
